Things are crazy right now. I'm kind of overwhelmed.
The chain on my collar's been cut, which eliminates any danger of the bomb inside of it from detonating, so that's good.
But the moment that chain was severed, so was the only thing I ever truly had, the connection to my master.
The only way an Angeloid finds meaning in her existence is by following her master's orders to the letter.
But now, who do I obey? What am I supposed to do with this new life?
Maybe I should seek out a new master. I wonder what Tomuki would think about that.
I will return to the Promised Land. The girl's locker room!
What goes through that head of his?
I can't hear the heart of him. What do you think?
How do I obey?
I can't hear the heart of him.
The beginning was the time
You suddenly suddenly appeared
When you were born before you
You were chosen
It's so true
No one had to own
Good little
I can hear my heart
I cannot pause
The 99ème tubes
Youаю the most
What are you up to?
Just building a new glider.
What's wrong?
I don't know what I'm supposed to do with myself anymore.
I'm all alone. I don't have a master.
And now you're a bird that can fly freely through the air.
I'd call that a welcome change from the norm.
Maybe.
You'll be fine. Give it a little while and I'm sure the answer you need will come to you in due time.
That means a lot. Hearing it like that makes sense. I think you may be right.
I hope you get to fly soon too, Sugata.
I told him we'd never go out.
Quantum conversion operating at 100%.
Metamorphosis stability all green.
At the present time, everything is looking favorable.
How are you holding up so far, master?
Favorable, yeah.
I might just start appreciating the joys of being stepped on.
You sound just fine.
Perfect. This is exactly what you should use the greatest combat weapon ever for.
Doesn't what you're doing seem the slightest bit ridiculous, Alpha?
Master ordered me to do this.
And you seem to be enjoying it.
Which I guess isn't a problem.
I just wish I had some orders from my master to carry out.
Tomaki!
Oh, hey. Is that you, Nymph?
I was just wondering if there's anything I can do to help.
I got some free time.
Yeah, no. I'm good.
Okay.
All right, Icarus.
Time to transform me into something else and move on.
So naughty.
Sorry to blow your minds, girls.
Tomoko's back.
And now it's time to charge into the tennis club's locker room.
Crap! Why the hell's Zahara here?
Master, the tennis club is still meeting in there.
She's a member.
Yeah, but that sucks.
As long as she's in there, my peeping day is ruined.
She knows who I am. I'm totally screwed.
Time for me to pitch in.
I know if I stuck around long enough, I'd be meeting for...
Everything up to now has been a warm-up.
That's all. The main event is on its way.
You're not going to give me an order.
I'm sick of gawking at bras and panties all the time.
That's why my next target is going to be a location like you've never seen.
A paradise where even more girls will be running around half-naked.
Welcome to the Satsukatane Swim Resort.
Please make yourselves at home.
What's mine is yours, as you well know.
I had no idea your family owned an indoor water park.
Seriously, that's beyond awesome.
There are quite a few people here.
Don't you plan on changing into a swimsuit, Sugata?
Sorry, these are the only clothes I own.
I have to say, Sahara, that's a big tube you have wrapped around you.
Yeah, that's because I can't swim.
If you'll recall, neither can Icarus.
An angeloid's wings soak up water, which become quite heavy and weigh us down.
If that's the case, nymphs should be able to swim just fine.
You don't have any wings to get waterlogged, so you won't drop like a stone.
Don't make fun of me!
I can swim with or without wings, so just shut up!
Let's see.
For your freaking information, angeloids are not designed to be able to swim!
Definitely not true.
Wow, is that true?
How to think of it?
Where is Tomoki?
He was here just a moment ago.
Where did he run off to now?
I mean, he was the one who said we could all go to the pool together in the first place.
I can't stand this anymore.
All the smoking hot bodies, the slick, wet, clingy swimsuits.
There's a richness you just can't get from bras and panties.
Tomoki!
Adios!
Where'd he go?
I've never been on one of these before.
Guess I just jump in here.
Oh, this isn't fun at all.
I'm 선택ing you.
Oh, my God.
Angers away.
It was right.
This place is paradise on earth.
Tomoki!
What has gotten into you?
You're acting like a lunatic!
I'm so sorry, I don't speak your language.
You don't speak the language?
Whatever, my money says you've been planning this
since before we even got here.
Hold up, just hear me out, would ya?
Look around you, Zohara, just look.
See all those faces? They're happy.
Makes this argument seem kind of silly, doesn't it?
I don't know, I guess maybe?
Nothing but smiling faces, at peace.
And of course, a veritable cornucopia of butts and boobies
bursting from the confines of their suits!
Beautiful young women prancing about in public
in broad daylight, half-naked of their own volition!
That's what the pool is!
If I can't come here to get my fill of the female voice,
then where would you have me go? Huh? Where?
What a bunch of self-serving hokas.
I'd say it's almost refreshing to see this bold approach
toward ogling.
If you'll excuse me.
Oh, yeah, Zohara.
If you still want to hit me, that's cool.
You just have to come out here to do it.
Zohara, let me handle this one.
What are you going to do?
I don't care who you are.
You're taking this too far.
Commence tomaki hacking!
What's this?
I can't swim!
What's happening?
What did you do to me?
Nothing special.
I just hacked your tiny brain
and put a block on all your memories involving swimming
so you can't do it anymore.
Fascinating.
So now tomaki will sink like a stone anytime he gets in the water.
Now if you try any more of your perverted crap,
you could drown.
That's kind of funny.
Yeah.
I think it's time for the rest of us to enjoy ourselves.
What?
Wait!
Guys!
No, please!
You can't do this!
This is cruel and unusual punishment!
Oh, God!
Does this mean my days of checking out half-naked hotties are over?
What's the point of even coming to the water park anymore?
Dear Grandpa, here I am at the pool
and I can't even enjoy the ladies.
My life has lost any semblance of meaning.
What do I do now?
Master.
Hey, Iris.
Are you doing all right?
It doesn't matter.
I'm just going to drift like this for the rest of my life.
Wherever the current takes me, that's where I'll go.
That slide is like a force of nature.
It's so strong.
Duh.
What's my freakin' problem?
Why am I so hung up on swimsuits?
Half-naked chicks are all right, but...
Icarus!
What is it, Master?
I have an important order for you.
You're lucky, Alpha.
Getting to have Tomaki give you orders.
Isn't the current moving kind of fast?
All is going according to plan, Master.
Heads up, I'm tossing a line.
My swimsuit is coming loose.
Alpha's gotta be behind this.
Tomaki probably ordered her to mess with the wave.
That's impossible!
My block and his brain should still be on place.
How is he doing this?
Suits coming off, female bodies thrashing about.
Your magic hoodoo's nothing.
I just gotta copy what I see them doing.
Oh, no, I'm not gonna make it.
I'm sinking! I'm gonna drown!
I don't wanna go out!
That's right, I forgot.
The lazy river is a circle.
I can just cruise around all I like.
I don't have to swim at all.
I'm gonna drown! I'm gonna drown!
Oh!
Oh, yeah! Definitely drowning!
All right, Tomaki.
Let's think about this rationally.
It's a simple matter, really.
Whether I drown, or whether I don't.
Whether I live, or whether I...
Tomo! Tomaki!
Huh?
Whoa! Grandpa!
Tomaki!
Go back!
It's not your time.
There's still something you have to do!
Something I have to do?
Grandpa?
Grandpa!
Master?
I thought I was a goner!
Huh?
Where did everyone go?
The pool was closed after the incident, so they went to go change out of their suits.
No! They're changing?!
So that's it. The pool day is over.
Thank you for the second chance, Grandpa.
I swear I will not let this life be for nothing!
Thanks for waiting, everyone.
Here we go. The ladies' changing room at the pool.
The final sanctuary.
Inside waits a world where bras, panties, and swimsuits are unnecessary!
Yes!
This is my new form!
This is what I am now!
Here we go!
She's putting me on!
I am climbing that stairway to adulthood!
So, which one of these fine Bettys is slipping me up her thighs?
Okay, this is weird.
Were my panties always so frickin' ugly?
Don't move! Don't you dare!
Move even a single inch in your dead meat!
Master, if you get too worked up, you know what will happen.
You're kidding me!
The scene was one far too gruesome to call a massacre.
All that can reasonably be said is we lost something that day.
Something sacred.
And what would that be, you ask?
I thought it was as obvious as the sun in the sky.
We lost our greatest warrior.
So we thank him.
Thank you, Tomaki, for giving us a dream.
Thank you for giving us hope.
Truly, my friend, thank you.
My friend, thank you.
Thank you.
Hey, keep me, take me.
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
It's just a piece of junk now.
Zahara broke my quantum converter.
You mean you still haven't gotten your fill of panties and boobs and stuff?
Hell no! How am I supposed to peep on the changing rooms now, huh?
There's always cool guy jamming.
If I invoke it, you can peep, do whatever,
and the girls won't notice you any more than the paint on the walls.
What are you waiting for? Invoke it! Do it, please! I'm begging you!
Sorry, not unless you order me to do it.
Uh, yeah, I don't know.
Come on! Nurse, why?
It's just, with my master gone, there's no one to give me orders,
so I'm kind of wandering around with no purpose.
Please, Tomoki, give me an order!
I can't do that, nymph.
How come? Don't you have any orders for me?
I'll do anything you need. Just tell me, what do you want me to do?
You need to decide that for yourself.
You can go wherever you want now. Do whatever you want.
That's free will. Welcome to it.
I just do whatever I want.
Tomoki.
Okay, let's go over the answers to the quiz.
Number one is the Pacific Rim.
She's being held by the sky.
She sent you an angel because she wanted you to help her, but that doesn't really matter anymore.
It's so interesting. She's never seen an angel enjoy herself so much before, or at all for that matter.
I came to you because I wanted your help as well.
But I think I'll just go to sleep instead.
Goodbye.
Although, I do have a favor to ask of you if you're willing to assist.
Don't forget about me, whatever you do.
Tomoki. Tomoki, come on. Wake up, would you?
Class is over and you're drooling.
Oh, man. That dream.
What? Same one as usual?
Yeah, an angel was babbling something to me. Can't remember what.
Think it had anything to do with Icarus and Nymph and all the craziness they keep stirring up?
I don't know.
You don't know? Well, if you don't, who the heck does?
I don't care. Look, it's whatever. Nothing beats my peace and quiet.
As long as you and me can enjoy our time together, it's enough for me.
Wow, I actually have to agree with you for once.
Hey, what about you? What kind of dreams do you have?
Like, did you have one last night?
Huh? Last night?
Zohara.
Tomoki.
Oh, Tomo! You rotten pervert!
No! It's way too embarrassing!
Oh, it must have been one heck of a dream.
Oh, gosh. Why would I even have dreamt something like that?
Is it because someday I might actually want to marry Tomo?
Zohara?
Huh? Sorry, I spaced out there. We gotta roll.
Sugata invited us over to his place after school, remember?
Huh? I totally forgot.
Wow. I can't believe it's already been a whole year.
Another trial flight? You're never gonna learn, are you?
Whatever. Good luck.
We'll be waiting down the way a bit for whenever you crash.
Sugata, I have a question.
Hm?
Why do you keep trying so hard at this? I mean, you failed over and over again, right?
Because I had a dream once. A dream where I soared through the sky. I know this will work.
A dream? That's nice. And just one more thing angeloids can't do.
Dreams you have while sleeping aren't the only kind there are.
You've got something you dream about, don't you? Something that you hope will come true?
Yeah, I guess I do.
I really want Tomoki to be my master, but I try not to think about it because I know it won't come true.
He told me I was free now and then he just walked away.
I don't know. Maybe he doesn't like me.
Hm. It's the exact opposite.
That was Tomoki's way of being nice to you.
That was... nice, huh?
So then, that means he doesn't hate me after all.
Hm. The wind's starting to pick up.
So are we go for launch?
We're go. There's enough wind for it, and while I'm not perfectly happy with the direction I'm about to go,
it shouldn't affect my takeoff.
I wish you great success in the sky.
I hope that somehow we all get to see our dreams come true.
For a far away new world!
It did it!
It's boring!
So, hey, Alpha!
Do you mind if I stay here from now on?
I would like that.
Even though I might take Tomoki away from you, you're sure?
Of course.
Whatever happens, Master will still be my master.
From now into eternity.
Forever.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Do you want to love with me?
It's right now.
What on earth was that?
Heaven's last property, Forte.